- Look at their T-shirts.
- Slag party.
Wish you'd let me organise
you a slag party, Shona.
- Every day's a slag party to you.
- Ha! Hey!
Good joke. Come here, did you get
something for Vish's dad for us?
- Did you see me get anything?
- No. We'll get something from the shop.
Course I got him something and
a card and signed it from us.
Gotten all nervy.
You said you didn't care if Mam met them.
Not about Mammy meeting Vish's
family, about you and Ma.
- You haven't talked to her in months.
- Oh, Shona, don't.
No, come on, she's old.
You have to forgive her.
- Move on. - She's only
old when she wants to be.
- What if she died?
- Mammy won't die. She's too stubborn.
Can't believe I said
that about Mammy dying.
We're too different,
we'll never get along.
You'll never get along?
You always got along.
- Look, they've gone, free slag mags.
- Grab me one.
I'll tell you what the problem is.
I'm stuck in the middle of this
bullshit and it's not fair.
Hey, Sho, Sho, look at this.
We will fight them on the beaches.
W-we will fight them on the grass!
Then we will come back to the
beaches for more beach fighting.
My babies!
- What happened to your leg?
- What happened to you?
Don't point it out or people
will notice. It's grand.
- You have a cane. You look mad.
- No, it's not a cane.
I only have it in case my
sports injury starts playing up.
Oh, God.
God, your hair's got so long!
You look like your father in the 70s!
So I look like a dead man? Thanks.
Here. Who's this?
It's Uncle Terry!
Mammy, stop now.
No silliness, this is a big day for
Shona. We'll be late for our train.
Oh, come on.
What's in this, Mammy? Jesus.
Just a few bricks. A little bit
of gold bullion in my knickers.
Do you know what, it's a bit of
a way off. Shall we get a taxi?
Yes, please.
Shona, don't be gentle with
me like I'm an old one.
It's just my hamstring, I'm fine.
We'll put you in a wheelchair
and roll you down the hill.
Do you know what you're like,
you're like Willy Wonka --
- Willy Wonka. - Let me finish.
And The Chocolate Factory.
I wasn't interrupting,
that's how conversations work.
And anyway, the film is called Willy Wonka
but the book is called Charlie
and the Chocolate Factory.
- You used to read me that.
- No, it's the opposite way around.
- Now. - What? - How come you're
allowed to interrupt but I'm not?
Because that's different
than interrupting a joke.
- You let someone get to the end of --
- It was a joke, was it?
- Yes. It would have made Shona laugh.
- Go on, the pair of yous!
Oh, God.
Wait, Richard the French
boy's dad will love this.
- What are you doing?
- Taking a picture of these coffee pods. Funny.
He says people recycle
them but no one ever does.
Who's Richard? You never told
me there was a man on the go.
- Oh, Mammy! - Well, Mammy,
Richard is Aine's elderly lover.
- Oh, elderly lover?
- He's the same age as Shona!
Do you think he might want
a go on the mother too?
- Oh! - Well, when I put my cane
down I could give it a good go.
Bleurgh! Disgusting!
Hey, girls.
Get off, get off, it was a joke!
I was being Willy Wonka!
Well, it's a joke if
you know how to do it.
You've no sense of humour.
I would have laughed so hard if it
backfired and you fell right on your face.
Anyways, that's not how you do a fall. It's
all in the feet. This is how you do a fall.
Like... Whoa!
- Like that.
- That was really fake.
I knew you were going to do that.
You knew because I told
you I was gonna do it.
Answer for everything. All
right, show me a back flip now.
I watched a YouTube clip
so don't be sarcastic.
Let's get a taxi, seriously.
Let's just get a taxi.
- Don't talk about curry or Bollywood.
- I could have worked in Bollywood.
I went for a casting for a music
video they made in Dublin once.
Who were they? All the Bollywoods?
Paul Bollywood and his friends?
There was an Indian gentleman we
interviewed one time for Nationwide.
Lovely man. Lived in Nice.
Er... Don't mention that. I
don't know why, just don't.
- And don't talk about marriage or...
- Yeah, Mam.
- I was talking to you. - What? - Ah.
Hi!
Come in, come in.
Hello! Hello!
- Happy birthday, Hari.
- Hello, how are you?
That's for you from all of us.
Today's not about me, I
don't want to make a fuss.
Oh, there she is! I just
wanted to meet the big star.
Oh no! No, just treat
me like a normal person.
What a lovely house you've got.
Hi, I'm your slave for today.
I don't get to eat never mind
that I'm on a zero hours contract.
- But would you like one of these?
- Tell me, what's in this one?
Mam, they're grand, you'll like them.
- I was only asking.
- Nothing is too spicy, Eileen.
We learnt our lesson from
the last time Aine was here.
It wasn't too spicy for me,
something just got stuck in my neck.
- Spice.
- She is very sensitive.
This is demeaning on so many levels.
If you got a proper job you could
have a spot at the big boys' table.
I have a proper job at BuzzFeed.
Oh, Bubs, you know what,
when you go to school and study hard
you could have a job at BuzzFeed.
Or you can do what Uncle Vish did and move to
New York for two minutes and sound like a shit
radio DJ.
Whoa, whoa, radio DJ!
It was 12 years, it wasn't two minutes.
Happy birthday to you, Dad.
Don't make a fuss, huh?
- You'll make him cry.
- All right, everyone, listen up. Shh.
I just want to say how wonderful it
is to have you here with us today.
And to celebrate we have
prepared a special dish for Aine.
Oh, that's so nice.
Ta da!
Very funny. Oh, my God, thank you so
much. Is this all the way from Kerala?
- No. Too spicy.
- Would you like yogurt with that?
Can I get some yoghurt, please? Thank you.
What you up to right now, Sho?
I haven't told you about Sho's new thing?
- You're gonna love this as a woman.
- As a woman who also has a job.
Listen up... working woman.
No, it is very good, Sho is doing this
networking thing for women in finance.
- Oh, wow, that's amazing.
- Yes, it is very exciting.
It's a big project. I'm setting it
up for this amazing woman who's...
- She's doing most of the work.
- She's more amazing.
- Oh, that's amazing!
- Is it a big job, Shona?
Mm. Yeah.
It's small right now but hopefully
over the next couple of years.
It'll be hard with the
children then, won't it?
- Mum!
- Well, what?
Time must be a pressure at this stage.
Oh, yes, none of us getting
any younger, Kavita.
Well, Shona doesn't have time
for kids cos she's got me.
Well, you definitely have become
a full-time job this last year.
What was last year?
Er, she broke her leg.
- Oh, no! What did you do? - Yeah.
- It's all fixed now. She's fine.
That's bad luck that
you both have bad legs.
That's where the similarity ends, Seema.
Actually, I once auditioned
for the film My Left Foot.
- Wowee! - What did you
audition for, the right foot?
No!
For a neighbour who comes in.
The neighbour, I think I saw that bit!
- Did you? - She didn't
get the part. Chill out.
I actually don't want kids.
You always think you don't want
kids and then you change your mind.
I mean, I still sometimes
think I don't want Aine.
But genuinely, I genuinely
don't, you know?
It's not a big deal. Just never have.
Do you know what, lads, I'm going
to throw caution to the wind
and eat with my hand!
Yeah, so fork off, forks.
What about you and children, Vish?
- Oh, erm, I want what Shona wants.
- Oh, OK.
What about when you're our age? Who'll
look after you in the care home?
- I thought you wanted kids, Vish.
- No, I er... I have Bubs right here.
And she is all I need and then
give her back to you when I'm done.
- You never know real love
until you have children. - Mam!
Even if Anil murdered someone I'd
still love him unconditionally.
And get a spade to dig a
grave and cover it up.
- Why am I a murderer?
- Vish'd never murder someone.
Yeah, I'm a pyro guy.
- Let me take her back.
- No, she's fine.
I don't think you need to be a
mother to know unconditional love.
Don't think that's a thing.
Also I have enough money to hire
someone to visit me in a care home so...
Do you know what, I'm just gonna make
a call, I'll be back in a second.
- This is new.
- Huh?
Oh, shit, I didn't mean to FaceTime you!
- Shall I call you back normally?
- It's OK. It's nice.
It's nice to see your face. Are you OK?
Yeah. I just literally saw a
picture of Vish and his ex-wife
in a frame in his parents' kitchen.
Oh, God, why do they still have that?
- No idea.
- Can I see it?
Oh, she's an angry little elf.
Yeah, er... It's thrown me a bit, sorry.
Long day. Erm...
Listen, I don't know if
this is a good time but --
- Sorry, Shona.
- It's OK.
I-I'll let you go. We can talk later.
Yeah, OK. All right, I'll call you back.
Shona, you know we don't
care if you have children.
Oh, no, no, it's not that. It's erm...
Oh, that's embarrassing.
No, it's fine, I get it. I mean,
it was his first marriage, it's...
Shona, we just like the
frame, that is why we have it.
- Really? - Genuinely, and that
woman was a complete idiot.
She thought France was
the capital of France.
Did she?
I've taken some really
nice pictures of you today.
I'm going to put you in it instead.
Oh no, you don't need
to put me in a frame.
I mean, it's a very nice frame.
I want you to help me choose
because I always get this wrong.
The women always get annoyed when I put
their picture on Instagram without editing.
All they want is a Valencia
filter and no smiling.
Wouldn't be the worst.
Sorry. They're awful.
Oh! So the sun is actually boiling
up the worm? That's disgusting.
Poor little wormie, he
needs to get inside.
- He's got no way because...
- Any reply from the old boy?
I'm not waiting for a reply from old
boy. What was that about the worm?
The worm crawled up...
- Isn't that nice?
- Mm.
He's a real softie, isn't he?
- Our Shona always loved
being round her dad. - Mm.
- What's he doing? Is he
flirting with you? - Yeah.
I said he could cos it's his birthday.
- We have this agreement.
- On any man's birthday...
I'm sorry, I just want both
of you to be happy. You know.
- Don't be silly. Don't worry.
- And honestly we do just love that frame.
- Harry told me.
- Right.
Well, it's a beautiful thing.
♪ Happy birthday to you
- Oh, no!
- ♪ Happy birthday to you
- Don't make a fuss.
- ♪ Happy birthday dear Dad
Oh, he's cry -- Dad! Whoa! No crying! Ah!
Come here!
Oh, Dad, why you crying?
It's your birthday!
It's only a cake, darling!
- Oh, Shona, could you
take a picture? - Yes!
With Harry's phone? OK...
- Smiles!
That's it! Ah.
Could somebody blow the candles
out before the house burns down.
- Birthday boy.
- One, two, three.
Go, go, keep going, keep going!
Last one!
Right, a song.
- Now, my two daughters --
- Oh, Mammy, we're not singing. Stop.
- Yes. They have the voices of angels.
- I don't think so.
No, you are going to sing.
- No. No.
- You can sing for your supper.
I can sing!
♪ Up above the world so high
♪ Like a diamond in the sky
♪ Twinkle twinkle little star
♪ How I wonder what you are
Go on. Sing the song.
Oh, no, Mammy, we're not singing.
- The one about the ghost.
- It's not about ghosts!
- Sing it!
- No!
♪ You see, it's not me, it's not my family
- ♪ In your head, in your head
- ♪ In your head
- ♪ They are fighting
- ♪ With their tanks and
their bombs - ♪ Tanks
- ♪ And their bombs and their guns
- ♪ Bombs
- ♪ In your head, in your head
- ♪ They are crying
- ♪ Cry
♪ In your he-ad
♪ In your he-ea-ad
♪ Zombie, zombie
♪ Zombie, eh-eh-eh
♪ Oh oh oh oh
♪ Oh-oh-oh, aye aye aye
♪ Ah... ♪
~
I feel like an absolute prick.
No, it's really good! Honestly.
- Very haunting.
- Is it?
That was... very good, Synthesiser Patel.
- I don't have a piano at home so...
- Well, you'd never know.
- You'd never know. - It's always
a skill to have, isn't it, piano?
- So will the movie star be singing?
- Oh, no, no, I shun the limelight.
- Oh, yeah, Mam, do a song.
- We don't, we do not any more.
- What?
- You used to love performing.
- I didn't, I hated it.
- She loved it. - I didn't.
She used to come on set with me
and she would walk up and down
modelling children's hats.
Because, you see, I used to wear a different
hat every day when I was doing the weath
er.
- We were a very popular item.
- We heard. So amazing.
- Shona...
- What? My finger slipped!
♪ You know, every now and then
- Just do it. - ♪ I think you might
like to hear something from us
- Go on, Ma. Do the duet.
- I don't want to!
♪ But there's just one thing
♪ We never ever do nothing nice and easy
Get up! ♪ We always do it nice and rough
- ♪ So we're gonna take the
beginning of this song easy - Do it!
♪ Then we're gonna finish it rough
♪ This is the way we do Proud Mary
♪ Cos we rolling
Yes! Here we go!
- ♪ Rolling
- Listen to the song.
♪ Rolling on the river
♪ Left a good job in the city
♪ I was working for the
man every night and day
♪ And I didn't miss a minute of sleeping
♪ Cos I was worrying about
the way things might have been
♪ You know the big wheels keep on turning
Here we go! ♪ Proud Mary keep on burning
♪ Cos we're rolling, rolling
♪ Rolling on the river
♪ Rolling, whoo! Rolling, whoo!
♪ Rolling on the river ♪
Really nice to see you.
You'll never get rid of us.
- Thank you so much for coming.
- Thank you. The food was delicious.
Where's your coat?
- I'm gonna stay here for a bit so you
two head back together, yeah? - What?
I'll bring your bag. Aine
has my key to let you in.
Er... But h-how will we
find the train station?
- We'll be grand if you draw us a map.
- No, you'll be grand
because you have phones and
you're not five years old.
- Right. - Right. - Bye,
see you back at your place.
- Love you.
- Love you too.
I really do.
- It's been lovely.
- Are you pissed off with me?
- I'm not pissed off with you.
- No tears, hmm?
- Thank you for a lovely day.
- Bye!
Your singing was really good.
Shouldn't have said to
Shona about having kids.
You shouldn't have been so narky
cos some old fella never texted you.
I work for him so just try and hurry
up, we're gonna miss this train.
Excuse me, that's my mother!
- Sorry.
- She's disabled. Jesus!
- Christ!
Mam, stop, you all right?
And you did love coming to set with me.
All those things I did. Like
wearing those stupid hats.
That's what paid for your drama
classes and Shona's riding lessons
- and all those Ad-eedas shoes.
- Adidas.
Adidas shoes.
I was just trying to do my best.
Yeah, well, your best
didn't work cos look at me.
Why you so angry all the time?
- What have I done? I didn't do anything.
- Exactly, Mammy! Exactly!
- You didn't do anything.
- What are you on about?
- You didn't come and get me.
- Come and get you? - Yes.
What?
I wanted you to come and get me, Mammy.
I wanted you to come down to that
place and take me out of there.
And take me home and make me better.
Those people in there
knew what they were doing.
What help would I have been?
You're my mammy, that's why!
I just wanted you to try.
Instead of all this... all this pretence,
like I'm fine, like everything's
fine, like it's grand.
- Like she broke her leg.
- That's what you told me to say.
Only to family if they
asked me where I was.
I was so alone, Mammy. You've no idea.
- Oh, I have an idea, believe
you me. I know. - Oh, really?
- Oh yeah, what, was bingo difficult
one night? - I bloody know.
I left Shona. When she
was born, I left her.
For three months I left her
because... I didn't want her.
Mam.
I just... I just couldn't.
I'm sorry, Mam.
- But you are brilliant.
- Oh... - You are.
And why wouldn't you be
brilliant? You're my daughter.
I just want you to find someone
who'll make you see that.
Mammy, a man isn't gonna fix me.
No.
- Bit of sex'd be nice.
- Oh, God, yuck, don't.
Oh and if you tell Shona
I left her I'll kill you.
And...
Well, could you just ring me sometimes.
You have to work out how to use
FaceTime. The top of your head --
It's very lonely, Aine.
Most of my friends, half of them are dead.
Did you kill them?
Only Louise Gallagher because
she was so fucking annoying!
- Oh, my God, Mammy, he texted back.
- Go on, what did he say?
Wait a minute.
"Ha ha."
That's a bit of an anticlimax.
Jesus.
You have to be careful with
men. They don't always get jokes.
No.
Also annoyingly Shona didn't
get us return tickets.
- What?
- Don't worry, I'll get them.
No, I'm getting the tickets.
- No, you're disabled so it'll be half price.
- I am not disabled.
I am getting both tickets and
they will both be full fares.