-Oh, my God, we did it.
-We just got married. Right there.
Is that your ring?
We're off to a good start.
You sure you're not pregnant?
Yeah,
but if you're ready to have kids. . .
. . .I'll blow off this party right now.
-That ceremony was so beautiful.
-Was it perfect?
Is it too soon to see the video?
Can we just take a moment?
Our two best friends just got married.
We are so blessed to be able
to share in this incredible joy.
That is so true.
Mon, is it too late to switch from
chicken to steak?
I'm so happy for you guys.
You were both so lucky.
You both said the right names.
And nobody was drunk.
Nobody was gay.
And on your first try!
The One After "I Do"
Great.
I'll just change the film.
I know I'm not supposed to know,
but I do and I'm so excited.
-What's going on?
-Monica's pregnant.
Is that why you had to get married?
-I'm not pregnant!
-Ah, slow swimmers?
-You're not pregnant?
-Did you tell anybody I was?
No.
I'll be right back.
You take a lot of pictures!
I'll just shoot Monica
and the bloody soldier.
-You gotta change before the party.
-I don't have any other clothes.
Find anything that doesn't say,
"I died tragically in France. "
Fine.
And be careful who you hug.
You got blood on my father's dress.
Let's see the bride and groom,
and the bridesmaids.
-Why did you say you're not pregnant?
-'Cause I'm not.
We found your test in the trash.
If you're not pregnant. . .
. . .it's because I am.
-What are you talking about?
-I am with child.
I didn't say anything
because it's your day.
So you told people I was pregnant?
Does this look like
a moment to remember?
-Who's the father?
-I can't say.
-Why not?
-I can't say because he's famous.
Oh, my God, who is it?
Come on, you have to tell us.
-Okay. It's James Brolin.
-James Brolin is the father.
-Barbra Streisand's husband?
What? He never said that to me.
Let's get Chandler
and the bridesmaids.
-How about just the bridesmaids?
-You know, I am the groom.
-Oh, my God!
-Thank you for doing that!
-You said Monica was pregnant.
-You did, I just didn't disagree.
Sneaky!
Smile, ladies!
-By the way, James Brolin?
-I know.
I could only think of two names:
him and Ed Begley Jr.
Then I remembered he's gay, so. . . .
-Ed Begley Jr. is not gay.
-Really?
-Congratulations!
-You married just in time, I hear.
What? Ross!
If you've got this under control,
I'm just--
I just wanted you to know
that you have given us more joy--
-Ma, I'm not pregnant.
-What?
Not pregnant.
Oh, well.
-But I did still get married today.
-Whatever.
Thank you very much. It gives me
great pleasure to introduce to you:
Mr. and Mrs. Chandler Bing!
-Before we go, I got a present.
-I won't put my hand in your pocket.
No.
I've been taking dancing lessons.
I wanted this to be memorable.
That is so sweet!
So will you join me in our first dance
as husband and wife?
-What is it?
-These new shoes are all slippery.
-Will you be able to do this?
-Not well.
Good news!
I don't think anyone's looking.
-Are you ready to talk about it?
-No.
Now?
No!
Okay, we'll talk about
something else. Who's the father?
I haven't told him yet, so I don't
think I should tell anybody else.
That's fair. Is it Tag?
I'm sorry, I'll stop.
Is it Ross?
-Oh, my God, it's Joey!
-Stop it.
I'm not telling you until I tell him.
At least we know it's a him.
-Oh, sweet Lord.
-I'm sorry, okay?
It was either this or a bathrobe.
What's more important?
My clothes, or being here today?
I'm not even going to pretend
to be listening.
I don't think we met.
I'm Ross, Monica's brother.
Hi, I'm Mona from the restaurant.
Hello, "Mona from the restaurant. "
-Mona. What a beautiful name.
-I always kind of hated it.
Come on! Mona Lisa?
Mona. . .
. . .Klegglachen?
The famous botanist.
She's-- Well, she's dead now.
But she was once
the hottie of the plant world.
-I never knew about her.
-Linda Klegglachen. . . .
So, what table are you at?
Me too.
Good. There will be
someone who likes my name.
Yes, there will.
Guess what, Molly Gilbert. You've
just been bumped up to table one.
If it's all right with you,
I'll take your place at table six.
Martin Klegglachen!
That's better. Bend your arms,
look straight ahead.
This time,
really put your ass into it.
Who's slippery now?
Doesn't it feel good, rubbing a fork
on the bottom of your shoe?
Look, my date has arrived.
I want you to meet Dennis Phillips.
-This is my son, Chandler.
-Congratulations.
Dennis is a dear old friend.
And a fantastic lover.
Are my ears bleeding?
Chandler has always been shy.
You're right. Bravo, Dennis,
thanks for pleasing my mother so.
I missed the ceremony
because I was at auditions.
Dennis is directing
a new Broadway show.
I've admired your work for years.
Thank you.
Excuse me, I'll get myself a drink.
I'll be back in a moment.
Okay, stop!
-Dennis Phillips! How did you meet?
-It's a funny story.
Funny "ha-ha," or funny--?
Thank you. If you'll take your seats,
dinner will be served.
-I thought you were at table six.
-No. Nine.
When you showed it to me,
you held it that way. . .
. . .which was misleading.
Hello.
Can you see if your mom can give
my résumé to Dennis Phillips?
They've kind of locked themselves
in the men's room.
Perhaps when they get out.
If I got a Broadway show,
then I would have done it all.
Film, television and theater.
Not radio, but that's for ugly people.
-What size shoes do you wear?
-Eleven.
My shoes are giving me a problem.
Can I borrow your boots?
I don't know where I left them, so. . . .
-Those aren't 1 1 s.
-Okay, fine, I'm a 7!
But the rest of me is good!
Who am I kidding,
I belong in radio.
-I can't believe Phoebe's pregnant.
-Let's not talk about that now.
-This is so huge.
-Sure, but as big as your wedding?
Of course not. Nothing is.
In this day and age, how dumb
do you have to be to get pregnant?
Sometimes you can wear
everything you're supposed to. . .
. . .and one of those little guys
just gets through.
-How?
-I don't know, maybe they have tools.
She said she's
definitely having the baby.
She's gonna raise it on her own.
Maybe that's really brave.
I just hope she realizes
how hard it's gonna be.
Maybe she hasn't really
thought it through that much.
There's a lot to think about.
How is she gonna
handle it financially?
Does she realize she's not gonna
have a date for the next 1 8 years?
-I don't know.
-Are you okay?
I'm just thinking
about poor, knocked-up Phoebe.
-Champagne?
-Thank you very much.
That's how the French drink it.
Well, I just got off the phone
with my lover, James Brolin.
-Really?
-And he is married to some singer.
But he said he'd leave her for me.
So I said, "Are you sure?"
-And he said--
-Rachel's pregnant?
What?
-Why bother?
-How do you feel?
I don't know.
I have to make all these decisions
that I don't want to make.
-Someone take this away from me!
-Maybe you're not pregnant.
When I got pregnant,
I took the test three times.
Yes. Are you sure
you peed on the stick right?
How many ways are there?
I'm just saying,
don't freak out until you're sure.
All right, I'll take it again
when I get home. I can wait.
This is a good party.
How late does it go till?
You gotta take it now. You won't
be able to have fun until we know.
-Do it as a present to me.
-Okay. Thank you.
-I'll run out and get you one.
-You're great.
Wait a minute. Who's the father?
-She won't tell us.
-Come on! It could be my present.
-I just gave you peeing on a stick.
-This is why you register.
It was the chair again.
I'm not doing it!
Dad, can't you go back to your table?
Apparently, little Molly Gilbert
is enjoying her grown-up salmon.
You know what. . .?
-Would you like to dance?
-Sure.
-Dr. Geller?
-I wasn't farting!
A little game from our table.
Dr. Geller, will you dance with me?
Maybe later.
I'm about to dance with this lady.
Unless this lady wouldn't mind
letting you go first.
I'd be happy to.
You are very sweet.
Yes, I am.
In fact, let's try my special way.
You can dance on my feet.
Hop on.
Is the pretty lady looking?
Keep dancing.
And the world will never know.
-Did you talk to Dennis?
-I told him how talented you were.
-And about Days of our Lives.
-No, you don't tell him that!
-He'll think I'm just a soap actor.
-But you're not!
You are a soap actor
with freakishly tiny feet.
He has no idea
what kind of range I have.
Don't move.
It's like he's running on pegs.
-Thank you.
-No, thank you, Miranda.
-Melinda.
-All right.
-How cute was that?
-Were you watching?
Can I go next?
Of course you can. Hop on.
But I get to hop on after her.
-I am so gonna score!
-What?
I like your bow.
I'd like to propose a toast
to Monica and Chandler. . .
. . .the greatest couple in the world,
and my best friends.
When I first found out they were
getting married, I was a little angry.
"Why, God? How can you
take them away from me?! "
But then I thought back over our
memories together.
Happy memories.
And there were some sad memories.
I'm sorry.
And some scared memories.
And then I realized
I'll always be their friend.
A friend who can speak
in many dialects. . .
. . .has training in stage combat
and is willing to do partial nudity.
To the happy couple.
-That was nice.
-Can we do it again?
No, no.
-So is it my turn?
-I'm next.
-Okay, you can dance with her first.
-Are you sure?
-What's your name?
-Gert.
That's pretty.
What are you doing, Gert?
Dancing on your feet
like the other girls.
Okay. Hop on, Gert.
-Why aren't you moving your feet?
-I'm trying.
You're not going fast enough.
Maybe I should stand on your feet!
Did you happen to catch my toast?
-Was that for my benefit?
-There was something for everyone.
-I know you're casting for a show.
-I don't think you're right for it.
You're wrong.
Whatever it is, I can do it.
-Try me.
-It's an all-Chinese cast.
Can you be Chinese?
-I'm not proud of this, but. . . .
-No, please!
-Want to go back to the dance floor?
-Did it turn into sand?
-Come on, you'll be fine.
-No, I won't.
Know why I took all those lessons?
I didn't want you to be embarrassed
to be seen with some clumsy idiot.
You could never embarrass me.
Okay, you could easily do that.
But it doesn't matter.
I married you. No matter what you do,
I'm going home with you.
So I'm gonna dance with my husband.
That's the last time I buy shoes
at the Slippery Fun shoe store.
Just try not to move your feet at all.
There you go.
I'm gonna have you arrested.
You stole my moves.
-You're quite the dancer.
-Thanks, Mrs. Geller.
-You can call me "Mom. "
-Really? I will.
What's the matter?
Sorry, Mom.
-How much longer?
-Thirty seconds.
Did I miss it?
Rachel, I want you to know. . .
. . .that if it's positive, we--
-I know.
-You do? Okay.
It's time.
No!
-Go ahead, Rach.
-I can't look at it.
Somebody tell me.
It's negative.
-What?
-It's negative.
Well, there you go.
That's really great, great news.
Because the whole. . .
. . .not being ready,
the financial aspects, all that. . . .
This is just the way
it was supposed to be.
Well then, great.
This is so stupid.
How can I be upset
over something I never had?
-It's negative?
-No, it's positive.
-What?
-It's not negative, it's positive.
-Are you sure?
-Yeah, I lied before.
-Now you know how you really feel.
-That's a risky little game.
Are you really gonna do this?
I'm gonna have a baby.
I'm gonna have a baby!
-With who?
-No, it's still not the time.
I didn't see
the fast song coming.
Don't try to talk. We'll get you
up to your room, soak your feet.
That's so sweet!
There's so few
genuinely nice guys out there.
I feel like I'm holding down
the fort all alone.
-It's Joey, right?
-Yeah.
Wait a minute! I'm the nice one!
I danced with the kids all night.
How small are your feet?
Subtitles by
SDI Media Group
[ENGLISH]